<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Spearfishing &#8211; Spearmex</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-tag/spearfishing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Luxury Fishing &#38; Spearfishing adventures in Punta Mita, Nayarit Mexico</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 19:29:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/favicon-100x100.png</url>
	<title>Spearfishing &#8211; Spearmex</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Discover Spearfishing</title>
		<link>/product/discover-spearfishing/</link>
					<comments>/product/discover-spearfishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 15:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dive into the food web and experience the thrill of the underwater hunt. Our discover spearfishing is an extraordinary excursion for families and friends alike.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You slide into the water as quietly as possible and take in the new world around you. Man, woman, girl, or boy; you are now a predator. You know your environment, recognize your prey, and have the underwater skills and cunning to bring your fish to the surface on a single breath.In an increasingly more interdependent society, who doesn’t daydream of a simple and direct relationship with our food; of recognizing our place in the earth’s order, embracing our primal nature, and celebrating the autonomy of a successful hunt and delicious meal.</p>
<p>Spearfishing, or underwater hunting, is fishing’s most selective and engaging practice; the only fishing style in which one can cross the threshold of the oceans surface to become an active part of the underwater ecosystem; blending enjoyment and exercise into a true ‘ocean to table’ experience.</p>
<p>Great for families, this Discover Spearfishing excursion is a life changing family activity that introduces your children to the complete energy cycle giving them skills and appreciation to last a lifetime.</p>
<p>Our trained spear divers will take you through the basics of underwater hunting. You will learn how to safely operate your spear and equipment, distinguish the edible fish of our reef areas, and develop the cunning and the underwater skills to stalk and shoot your first underwater catch.</p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>3-hour expedition</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit® drinks, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/discover-spearfishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blue Water Hunting</title>
		<link>/product/blue-water-hunting/</link>
					<comments>/product/blue-water-hunting/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=484</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This excursion is the perfect combination of on-board luxury and raw adrenaline as we head into the world class fishing waters of Pacific Mexico for the ultimate open ocean spearfishing adventure.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="row">
<div class="col-md-9">
<p>Our most outstanding experience, the Blue Water Hunting expedition is unlike any other. Offshore is where fish stories need no exaggeration… Dozens of Mahi-mahi circling under a driftwood log, Marlin moving in and out of a bait ball, Yellow fin Tuna schools barreling past as you dive into the open blue… and of course the pure adrenaline rush of a thrilling and successful hunt.Explore the crystal clear offshore waters of the Mexican Pacific, home to some of the healthiest fishing grounds in the world teeming with yellow fin tuna, mahi-mahi, wahoo, and more. Gain an extra edge as our RIFFE team’s professional diver, Sebastian Melani, shares his personal tips on equipment use, dive techniques, and the local area, conditions, and game.</p>
<p>Our fully equipped boats and seasoned team of free divers and captains will assure a first-class experience. Enjoy freshly made ceviche from the day’s first catch prepared by our chef and paired with our specially made seasonal fruit drinks as part of our Patron Experience<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />.</p>
</div>
<div class="col-md-3">
<p><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-1800 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna.png" alt="" width="437" height="218" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna.png 437w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna-300x150.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna-162x81.png 162w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna-104x52.png 104w" sizes="(max-width: 437px) 100vw, 437px" /><br />
Yellowfin Tuna/Atun Amarilla</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-1799 size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-300x124.png" alt="Mahi Mahi/Dorado" width="300" height="124" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-300x124.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-162x67.png 162w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-126x52.png 126w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi.png 465w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><br />
Mahi Mahi/Dorado</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-1797 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo.png" alt="Wahoo/Wahoo" width="465" height="140" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo.png 465w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo-300x90.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo-162x49.png 162w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo-173x52.png 173w" sizes="(max-width: 465px) 100vw, 465px" /><br />
Wahoo/Wahoo</p>
</div>
</div>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hours expedition</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Melton tackle, Fish Cleaning , Vacuum Sealing and Deep Freeze catch</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit® drinks, sodas) and snacks (chicken wraps, fruits selection and cookies)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
<li>Patron Experience</li>
<li>Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/blue-water-hunting/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inshore Spearfishing</title>
		<link>/product/spearfishing-inshore/</link>
					<comments>/product/spearfishing-inshore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tropical reefs, thrilling spear opportunities, sunrises/sunsets, and family fun; this spearfishing excursion is chock full of memorable adventure for all.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Explore the area’s rich reef ecosystems in search of gourmet fish species… many not often found on the commercial market… while also enjoying the dynamic volcanic reef structures and tropical marine fauna. Up your game with valuable local knowledge from our spear guides on the reef’s edible fish, their behavior and terrain, and the appropriate gear and techniques for each species. Refine your camouflage and ambush techniques while searching the reef’s caves for delicious snapper species… or get into the action as jacks or Spanish mackerels raid the reef edge.</p>
<p>This half-day excursion is excellent for the whole family and/or groups of friends. For the best hunting opportunity, either head out at dawn for an early morning on the reef or enjoy the prime-time afternoon hours complete with a spectacular Pacific sunset on the ride back to port.</p>
<p>Topping off this well-rounded adventure are luxury amenities including fresh ceviche prepared from your first catch accompanied by seasonal fruit drinks, all compliments of our Patron Experience<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />.</p>
<p><strong>A spearfishing adventure for all to remember!</strong></p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>4 hours expedition</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Melton tackle, Fish Cleaning , Vacuum Sealing and Deep Freeze catch</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit® drinks, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
<li>Patron Experience</li>
<li><span style="font-size: 1rem;">Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/spearfishing-inshore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inshore Fishing</title>
		<link>/product/inshore-fishing/</link>
					<comments>/product/inshore-fishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=81</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Packed with adventure and sprinkled with luxury, this in-shore fishing excursion boasts an unforgettable adventure for the whole family.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While serious enough for experienced anglers to enjoy, this half-day expedition is ideal for families or groups looking for a casual or first-time fishing adventure. Balancing exhilarating fishing action with a leisurely cruise, this trip has something for everyone to enjoy.</p>
<p>Seasonal changes offer an enormous diversity of local marine fauna to appreciate throughout the year. Cruise Punta Mita’s coastal waters pursuing everything from jumping Spanish Mackerels and tasty Mahi-Mahi to tenacious Roosterfish (catch &amp; release species) and reef dwelling Snappers.</p>
<p>Our expert fishing staff and finest equipment insure a rewarding catch and gripping adventure for all. Onboard amenities add a touch of luxury to this trip, making it a delightful excursion for the entire family. Enjoy a ceviche prepared with your first catch of the day and paired with our exclusive Patron Experience<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> signature drinks as you revel in the natural wonders of the Pacific.</p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>4 hours expedition</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit®, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
<li>Patrón Experience</li>
<li>Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/inshore-fishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Game Fishing</title>
		<link>/product/big-game-fishing/</link>
					<comments>/product/big-game-fishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=86</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">A day-long, new exciting family adventure where you can catch your next big fish in the most spectacular offshore locations of Punta Mita. An adventure worthy of world record breaking.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This excursion is a must for any serious sportfishing angler looking for their next big catch. World Renowned in the fishing world, Punta Mita has welcomed numerous tournaments and repetitively boast world record catches. Sebastian Melani and his seasoned team at Spearmex offer a premier big game fishing adventure in luxurious style.</p>
<p>Visit offshore locations teeming with marlin, sailfish, yellow fin tuna, mahi-mahi, and more. Our fully equipped boats and professional team assure the very best chances for the catch of a lifetime. All of our expeditions are preformed with respect for the environment and billfish species are managed as catch and release only.</p>
<p>The Spearmex team caters to all, from the novice to the most experienced angler, making this a welcome expedition for family and friends. Enjoy top-notch amenities including gourmet ceviche or sashimi prepared from the day’s first catch by your personal chef and accompanied by our Patron Experience<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> signature drinks.</p>
<p><strong>Spearmex brings luxury into wild Pacific waters to create an unsurpassed deep-sea fishing adventure!</strong></p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>8-hour expedition</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Melton tackle, fish cleaning , vacuum sealing and deep freeze catch</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit, sodas) and snacks (chicken wraps, fruits selection and cookies)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
<li>Patron Experience</li>
<li>Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/big-game-fishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Basic Freediving</title>
		<link>/product/discover-freediving/</link>
					<comments>/product/discover-freediving/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 10:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Learn basic freediving principles and focus on practicing breathhold techniques in a pool or confined water site.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Freediving has been captivating the world for years with romantic visions of lone divers in the deep blue, unprecedented marine-life encounters, and the alluring discipline of moving meditation. Now it is your chance to immerse yourself in a magnificent underwater world that can only be experienced from within. A truly intriguing way to explore the aquatic realm, the practice of free diving is simultaneously a personal challenge and an experience of bliss; both an exercise and a meditation; a solo act that at the same time creates a feeling of unity and belonging.</p>
<p>Whether your goal is to become part of the reef or dive into the endless blue, Spearmex will introduce you to the best local sites appropriate for your skill level. Our certified instructors will share tips and techniques for deeper dives and richer adventures while allowing the safest and most enjoyable day on (and under) the water.</p>
<p>The internal discipline of diving to depths on a single breath welcomes the absolute best in marine life encounters… and Pacific Mexico has the best to offer with dynamic volcanic reefs, hearty marine life, and clean nutrient rich waters. Come and challenge yourself to explore the beauty of the ocean in a compelling new way.</p>
<h5 style="text-align: right;">“Man has only to sink beneath the surface and he is free.” -Jacques Yves Cousteau</h5>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>To enroll in a PADI Basic Freediver course you must be 12 years old or older. You need adequate swimming skills and need to be in good physical health. No prior experience with snorkeling, skin diving or freediving is required.</p>
<p><strong>The PADI Basic Freediver course consists of two main phases:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Knowledge development through independent study with the PADI <em>Freediver eLearning</em> (or your instructor may conduct class sessions if not available in a language you understand).</li>
<li>Confined water session to learn breathhold techniques as well as static and dynamic apnea, plus proper buddy procedures. Goal – static apnea of 90 seconds and dynamic apnea of 25 metres/80 feet</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>3-hour experience</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit, sodas) and snacks (chicken wraps, fruits selection and cookies)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/discover-freediving/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PADI Freediver</title>
		<link>/product/freediving-level-1/</link>
					<comments>/product/freediving-level-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 09:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=96</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Your first step toward discovering why freediving is becoming a popular way to explore beneath the waves. No previous freediving course is required.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="row">
<div class="col-md-8 col-lg-9">Experience freediving with Pacific Mexico’s one and only freediving academy, Spearmex, Gain the skills and confidence to take on diving’s purest discipline… one of mind and body.</div>
<div class="col-md-8 col-lg-9"><span style="font-size: 1rem;">In this complete PADI Freediver course, you will learn the most relevant techniques to train and adapt your body to be as efficient as possible while apnea diving. You will learn techniques to calm the mind and be introduced to the physiological changes your body undergoes while diving.</span></div>
<div class="col-md-8 col-lg-9"></div>
<div class="col-md-8 col-lg-9">
<p>Some take up free diving as a sport to challenge their human limits or as a mental discipline to compliment their yoga and meditation practices. Many just want to take snorkeling to the next level; experience the underwater world from within and enjoy more intimate marine life encounters. For others, free diving is the first step towards spearfishing, to bring a sense of autonomy into a modern lifestyle by hunting their own food.</p>
<p>Whatever your goals…</p>
<p><strong>Your journey begins here!</strong></p>
</div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="col-md-4 col-lg-3">
<blockquote>
<div class="dictionary"><strong>ap·ne·a</strong><br />
<span class="pron">[ ap-nee-uh ]</span><br />
<em>temporary cessation of breathing</em></div>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<div class="dictionary"><strong>free·div·ing</strong><br />
<span class="pron">[ free-dai-vuhng]</span><br />
<em>diving under the water independent of the use of breathing apparatus, especially in deep water.</em></div>
</blockquote>
</div>
</div>
<p>To enroll in a PADI Freediver course you must be at least 15 years old. You need adequate swimming skills and need to be in good physical health. No prior experience with snorkeling, skin diving or freediving is required.</p>
<h2>Academic</h2>
<p><strong>The PADI Freediver course consists of three main phases:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Knowledge development about freediving principles through independent study with PADI <em>Freediver eLearning</em> (or your instructor may conduct class sessions if not available in a language you understand).</li>
<li>Confined water session to learn breathhold techniques as well as static and dynamic apnea. Goal – static apnea of 90 seconds and dynamic apnea of 25 metres/80 feet.</li>
<li>Open water sessions to practice free immersion and constant weight freedives, plus proper buddy procedures. Goal – constant weight freedive of 10 metres/30 feet.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>2-day course</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit® drinks, sodas) and snacks (chicken wraps, fruits selection and cookies)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/freediving-level-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kayak Fishing</title>
		<link>/product/kayak-fishing/</link>
					<comments>/product/kayak-fishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 08:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=87</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This one-of-a-kind fishing experience combines the adrenaline of hooking a good catch and the challenge of maneuvering your kayak at the same time.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paddle out at dawn on out a custom-made fishing kayak for a unique, true life ‘Old Man and the Sea’ epic.</p>
<p>Our Jackson® fishing kayaks are equipped with the very best fishing equipment and experienced guides accompany you on your journey to lead you through an hour of the most unique fishing experience offered. Chance upon catches of jacks, snapper, pompano, and other coastal and reef fish while simultaneously handling your fishing vessel.</p>
<p>This excursion has gained fans all over the world due to the level of difficulty that it brings. Are you up for the challenge?</p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>2-hour expedition</li>
<li>1 hour expedition U$D 100.00</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit®, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Guide and Deckhands</li>
<li>Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/kayak-fishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Advanced Freediver</title>
		<link>/product/freediving-level-2/</link>
					<comments>/product/freediving-level-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=472</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Designed to refine and improve your freediving skills, allowing you to progress slowly while learning how your body performs during apnea (suspension of breathing).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Designed to refine and improve your freediving skills, allowing you to progress slowly while learning how your body performs during apnea (suspension of breathing).</strong></p>
<p>Achieving a new freediving time or reaching a new depth is an incredible feeling. It satisfies that very personal desire to do your best and be proud of what you can accomplish. The PADI Advanced Freediver course is designed to fulfill that personal need to refine and improve your freediving skills, allowing you to progress slowly while learning how your body performs during apnea.</p>
<p>To enroll in a PADI Advanced Freediver course you must be at least 15 years old and have a PADI Freediver certification (or a qualifying certification from another freediver organization). You also need to have Emergency First Response Primary and Secondary Care (CPR and First Aid) training within the past 24 months. You can complete this training during the Rescue Diver course. Your instructor may also offer the PADI Emergency Oxygen Provider Specialty course at the same time.</p>
<h2>Academic</h2>
<p><strong>The PADI Advanced Freediver course consists of three main phases:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Knowledge development about advanced freediving techniques and equipment. You’ll study independently using the PADI Freediver eLearning (or your instructor may conduct class sessions if not available in your language).</li>
<li>Confined water session to learn stretching and relaxation techniques as well as refine static and dynamic apnea. Goal – static apnea of 2 minutes, 30 seconds (2 minutes for freedivers younger than 18) and dynamic apnea of 50 metres/165 feet (40 metres/130 feet for freedivers younger than 18)</li>
<li>Open water sessions to practice deeper free immersion and constant weight freedives, along with additional buddy procedures and rescue techniques. Goal – constant weight freedive of 20 meters/65 feet (15 metres/50 feet for freedivers younger than 18)</li>
</ul>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>3-day course</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit, sodas) and snacks (chicken wraps, fruits selection and cookies)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/freediving-level-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
