<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Spearfishing &#8211; Spearmex</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/spearfishing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Luxury Fishing &#38; Spearfishing adventures in Punta Mita, Nayarit Mexico</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 19:29:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/favicon-100x100.png</url>
	<title>Spearfishing &#8211; Spearmex</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Discover Spearfishing</title>
		<link>/product/discover-spearfishing/</link>
					<comments>/product/discover-spearfishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 15:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dive into the food web and experience the thrill of the underwater hunt. Our discover spearfishing is an extraordinary excursion for families and friends alike.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You slide into the water as quietly as possible and take in the new world around you. Man, woman, girl, or boy; you are now a predator. You know your environment, recognize your prey, and have the underwater skills and cunning to bring your fish to the surface on a single breath.In an increasingly more interdependent society, who doesn’t daydream of a simple and direct relationship with our food; of recognizing our place in the earth’s order, embracing our primal nature, and celebrating the autonomy of a successful hunt and delicious meal.</p>
<p>Spearfishing, or underwater hunting, is fishing’s most selective and engaging practice; the only fishing style in which one can cross the threshold of the oceans surface to become an active part of the underwater ecosystem; blending enjoyment and exercise into a true ‘ocean to table’ experience.</p>
<p>Great for families, this Discover Spearfishing excursion is a life changing family activity that introduces your children to the complete energy cycle giving them skills and appreciation to last a lifetime.</p>
<p>Our trained spear divers will take you through the basics of underwater hunting. You will learn how to safely operate your spear and equipment, distinguish the edible fish of our reef areas, and develop the cunning and the underwater skills to stalk and shoot your first underwater catch.</p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>3-hour expedition</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit® drinks, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/discover-spearfishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blue Water Hunting</title>
		<link>/product/blue-water-hunting/</link>
					<comments>/product/blue-water-hunting/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=484</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This excursion is the perfect combination of on-board luxury and raw adrenaline as we head into the world class fishing waters of Pacific Mexico for the ultimate open ocean spearfishing adventure.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="row">
<div class="col-md-9">
<p>Our most outstanding experience, the Blue Water Hunting expedition is unlike any other. Offshore is where fish stories need no exaggeration… Dozens of Mahi-mahi circling under a driftwood log, Marlin moving in and out of a bait ball, Yellow fin Tuna schools barreling past as you dive into the open blue… and of course the pure adrenaline rush of a thrilling and successful hunt.Explore the crystal clear offshore waters of the Mexican Pacific, home to some of the healthiest fishing grounds in the world teeming with yellow fin tuna, mahi-mahi, wahoo, and more. Gain an extra edge as our RIFFE team’s professional diver, Sebastian Melani, shares his personal tips on equipment use, dive techniques, and the local area, conditions, and game.</p>
<p>Our fully equipped boats and seasoned team of free divers and captains will assure a first-class experience. Enjoy freshly made ceviche from the day’s first catch prepared by our chef and paired with our specially made seasonal fruit drinks as part of our Patron Experience<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />.</p>
</div>
<div class="col-md-3">
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-1800 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna.png" alt="" width="437" height="218" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna.png 437w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna-300x150.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna-162x81.png 162w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna-104x52.png 104w" sizes="(max-width: 437px) 100vw, 437px" /><br />
Yellowfin Tuna/Atun Amarilla</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-1799 size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-300x124.png" alt="Mahi Mahi/Dorado" width="300" height="124" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-300x124.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-162x67.png 162w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-126x52.png 126w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi.png 465w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><br />
Mahi Mahi/Dorado</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-1797 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo.png" alt="Wahoo/Wahoo" width="465" height="140" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo.png 465w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo-300x90.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo-162x49.png 162w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo-173x52.png 173w" sizes="(max-width: 465px) 100vw, 465px" /><br />
Wahoo/Wahoo</p>
</div>
</div>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hours expedition</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Melton tackle, Fish Cleaning , Vacuum Sealing and Deep Freeze catch</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit® drinks, sodas) and snacks (chicken wraps, fruits selection and cookies)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
<li>Patron Experience</li>
<li>Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/blue-water-hunting/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inshore Spearfishing</title>
		<link>/product/spearfishing-inshore/</link>
					<comments>/product/spearfishing-inshore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tropical reefs, thrilling spear opportunities, sunrises/sunsets, and family fun; this spearfishing excursion is chock full of memorable adventure for all.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Explore the area’s rich reef ecosystems in search of gourmet fish species… many not often found on the commercial market… while also enjoying the dynamic volcanic reef structures and tropical marine fauna. Up your game with valuable local knowledge from our spear guides on the reef’s edible fish, their behavior and terrain, and the appropriate gear and techniques for each species. Refine your camouflage and ambush techniques while searching the reef’s caves for delicious snapper species… or get into the action as jacks or Spanish mackerels raid the reef edge.</p>
<p>This half-day excursion is excellent for the whole family and/or groups of friends. For the best hunting opportunity, either head out at dawn for an early morning on the reef or enjoy the prime-time afternoon hours complete with a spectacular Pacific sunset on the ride back to port.</p>
<p>Topping off this well-rounded adventure are luxury amenities including fresh ceviche prepared from your first catch accompanied by seasonal fruit drinks, all compliments of our Patron Experience<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />.</p>
<p><strong>A spearfishing adventure for all to remember!</strong></p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>4 hours expedition</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Melton tackle, Fish Cleaning , Vacuum Sealing and Deep Freeze catch</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit® drinks, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
<li>Patron Experience</li>
<li><span style="font-size: 1rem;">Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/spearfishing-inshore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
