<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized | Spearmex</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Luxury Fishing &#38; Spearfishing adventures in Punta Mita, Nayarit Mexico</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:09:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/favicon-100x100.png</url>
	<title>Uncategorized | Spearmex</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ancora</title>
		<link>/product/ancora/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=2602</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Anclote Beach Condo, Punta de Mita]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[Anclote Beach Condo, Punta de Mita]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultimate Overnight Fishing Adventure</title>
		<link>/product/ultimate-overnight-fishing-adventure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=2549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join us for the ultimate fishing adventure! Experience the thrill of the Tuna grounds, where northern currents converge, creating perfect conditions for an unforgettable journey. Immerse yourself in the action as sardines and bait fish gather along the scenic canyon, accompanied by bird piles, dolphins, and tunas of all sizes. Our expert crew ensures an incredible day on the water, whether you're a spearfishing enthusiast diving straight into the action or prefer the thrill of rod and reel. Depart from Marina La Cruz at 7 pm, enjoy a delicious dinner on board, and embark on an overnight cruise to the Tuna grounds located 100 miles south. Spend the day bird pile hopping and mastering the art of spearfishing or live bait fishing. With the sunset as our backdrop, we'll cruise back to the marina, arriving just before sunrise. Indulge in an early morning breakfast before disembarking, cherishing the memories of this remarkable adventure. Book your spot today and get ready for an exhilarating fishing experience like no other.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When winter hits, the northern currents stir up a frenzy along the 20-mile offshore canyon, attracting sardines, bait fish, and a host of predators, from dolphins to massive tunas. Dive straight into the heart of the action with a loaded speargun or set up live bait for your rod and reel.</p>
<p>We kick off the adventure at 7 pm, feasting on dinner as we cruise overnight to the Tuna grounds 100 miles south. Brace yourself for a day of bird pile hopping, spearfishing, or live bait action. After chasing the sunset, we head back to the marina just before sunrise were breakfast will be served to disembark right after.</p>
<p>Gear up for the angler&#8217;s dream – our overnight fishing expedition from Marina La Cruz, priced at 1950 USD per person based on a minimum of 4 people.<br />
Including round trip from the airport to the marina and back. Travel in comfort and style aboard our adventure truck, ensuring you kick off and conclude your angling adventure with utmost convenience, all meals, a bar stock with beer &amp; white wine and all the essentials to keep you fueled and ready for action such as water, electrolyte, soft drinks, spearfishing &amp; fishing gear, bait and fishing license.</p>
<p>Mezcalitas, Margaritas &amp; Champagne available at additional cost. As well as vacuum seal service for your catch.</p>
<p>If one day isn&#8217;t enough, extend the thrill with an extra night/day at USD 3,900. Drop anchor at any of the secluded protected coves along the Jalisco/Colima costline, and keep the action rolling.</p>
<p>Get ready to reel in the big ones and live the hardcore angler life. Secure your spot now – this is not your average fishing trip! ?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
