<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Products &#8211; Spearmex</title>
	<atom:link href="/experiences/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Luxury Fishing &#38; Spearfishing adventures in Punta Mita, Nayarit Mexico</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 23:50:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Jet Ski &#038; Tow Sports</title>
		<link>/jet-ski/</link>
					<comments>/jet-ski/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 17:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=2060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Enjoying tow sports from our JetSki has never been easier thanks to three exclusive features including the retractable LinQ ski pylon, ski mode, and wakeboard rack.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jet-ski/">Jet Ski &#038; Tow Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Sea Doo Wake Pro 230</h2>
<p>Enjoying tow sports from our JetSki has never been easier thanks to three exclusive features including the retractable LinQ ski pylon, ski mode, and wakeboard rack.</p>
<p>The first fully-integrated waterproof Audio System will keep the fun going anywhere you go, standard with 100 watts of total system power, fully-waterproof performance, Bluetooth connectivity, and external playback controls to ensure the perfect song is always on!</p>
<p><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>BRP Audio &#8211; Premium Soundsystem</li>
<li>Direct-access front storage</li>
<li>Watertight phone compartment</li>
<li>Boarding Ladder</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>ACTIVITIES AVAILABLE</strong></h3>
<p><strong>FOIL SURFING</strong></p>
<p>Foilsurfing shifts that paradigm and completely redefines what kind of wave will get your heart racing.</p>
<p>Your first foilsurfing lesson takes place in the waterway where the water is flat, so you can learn the basics of riding a foilboard. Once you&#8217;ve got the hang of foiling in flat water, we will advance you to the next step by taking you out into the ocean where we&#8217;ll begin towing into ocean swell.</p>
<p>This is where you will learn how to catch and ride the swell energy and begin to learn the mechanics of pumping the foil to stay on the swell.</p>
<p><strong>WIND FOILING</strong></p>
<p>Windfoiling is relatively easy to learn, especially if you already know how to windsurf. The first few runs will be challenging as you need to get used to controlling the foil with small body movements. Pretty quickly you will finally understand the influence of your body weight and find the right position on your board.</p>
<p>Windfoiling is also far less physically demanding than windsurfing. Since you&#8217;ll be flying above the sea, there is no friction between the water and your board. The hydrodynamic drag is minimal and you don&#8217;t get battered around by the waves.</p>
<p>This makes windfoiling suitable for everybody, regardless of age or gender.</p>
<p><strong>WAKE FOILING</strong></p>
<p>Learning to how to foil is easy when you book a lesson with one of our experienced and knowledgeable coaches. Trying to figure it out on your own, on the other hand, can be a deeply intimidating and frustrating experience. When you learn with us, we&#8217;ll get you up on the foil the faster and safer way. Getting your first rides behind a jet ski dramatically simplifies and accelerates the learning curve.</p>
<p>Instead of guessing and learning by trial and error, our coaches will teach you the mechanics of foiling through a gradual progression on equipment that makes it as easy and safe as possible. Whether you are interested in foiling with a kite, a boat, or in the waves, we can get you where you want to go.</p>
<p><strong>WAKEBOARDING</strong></p>
<p>The wake board is another popular choice on the water and you don’t have to be able snowboard or water ski to enjoy wakeboarding. It’s a sport that provides a sense of achievement and thrills even for even complete novices. Do not miss the opportunity of a Wakeboarding sesion.</p>
<p>Allow yourself to relax allows your body to make changes and shift weight far easier than if you are tensed up. Before you are towed, you will start with the cable in hand and your knees drawn up as far as possible to your chest. Your arms should be stretched out in front of you.</p>
<p>Wakeboarding is all about going with the flow; once you feel the cable being pulled, allow yourself to roll forward slightly and keep your knees locked as your speed increases. Before you know it, you will be standing upright!</p>
<p><strong>DONUT RIDING</strong></p>
<p>An inflatable tube which is designed to be like a donut is towed behind a watercraft. Immerse yourself in the experience of speed and thrill as you glide on the water. You not only get to be on the Donut while having a time of your life but you’ll also be able to soak in the amazing coastline.</p>
<p>This amazing activity shouldn’t be missed especially by those who live for the high speed and thrill. With its twist and turns, high speed, it’ll surely test your strength while having the wildest ride of your life.</p>
<p>Our donut ride is a great choice for anyone new to watersports. It is also an amazing way to introduce young kids to the world of watersports. As this activity is suitable for everyone, we take extra measures for children and new adventurers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jet-ski/">Jet Ski &#038; Tow Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/jet-ski/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Advanced Open Water Diver</title>
		<link>/advanced-open-water-diver/</link>
					<comments>/advanced-open-water-diver/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 22:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1904</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This course can be taken after completing the PADI Open Water Diver certification. It's titled PADI Advanced Open Water Diver because it advances your diving knowledge &#38;amp; skills.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/advanced-open-water-diver/">Advanced Open Water Diver</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>This course can be taken after completing the PADI Open Water Diver certification. It&#8217;s titled PADI Advanced Open Water Diver because it advances your diving knowledge &amp; skills.</strong></p>
<p>That’s what the PADI Advanced Open Water Diver course is all about. You don’t have to be “advanced” to take it – it’s designed to advance your diving, so you can start right after earning your PADI Open Water Diver certification. The course helps build confidence and expand your scuba skills through different Adventure Dives. You try out different specialties while gaining experience under the supervision of your PADI Instructor. You log dives and develop capabilities as you find new ways to have fun scuba diving.</p>
<h2>Academic</h2>
<p>You’ll plan your learning path with your instructor by choosing from a long list of Adventure Dives. There are two required dives – Deep and Underwater Navigation – and you choose the other three, for a total of five dives.<br />
During the Deep Adventure Dive, you learn how to plan dives to deal with the physiological effects and challenges of deeper scuba diving. The Underwater Navigation Adventure Dive refines your compass navigation skills and helps you better navigate using kick-cycles, visual landmarks and time.</p>
<p>The other knowledge and skills you get vary with your interest and the adventures you have – photography, buoyancy control, fish identification, exploring wrecks and many more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/advanced-open-water-diver/">Advanced Open Water Diver</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/advanced-open-water-diver/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Water Diver</title>
		<link>/open-water-diver/</link>
					<comments>/open-water-diver/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 22:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Diver certification begins here. Start with PADI's online eLearning course. Move to the pool and practice your new skills. Then experience four open water (ocean/lake) dives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/open-water-diver/">Open Water Diver</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Diver certification begins here. Start with PADI&#8217;s online eLearning course. Move to the pool and practice your new skills. Then experience four open water (ocean/lake) dives.</strong></p>
<p>If you’ve always wanted to take scuba diving lessons, experience unparalleled adventure and see the world beneath the waves, this is where it starts. Get your scuba diving certification with the PADI® Open Water Diver course – the world’s most popular and widely recognized scuba course. Millions of people have learned to scuba dive and gone on to discover the wonders of the aquatic world through this course. To enroll in a PADI Open Water Diver course (or Junior Open Water Diver course), you must be 10 years old or older. You need adequate swimming skills and need to be in good physical health. No prior experience with scuba diving is required.</p>
<h2>Academic</h2>
<p><strong>The PADI Open Water Diver course consists of three main phases:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Knowledge Development ( <a href="https://apps.padi.com/scuba-diving/elearning/">online</a>, independent study or in a classroom) to understand basic principles of scuba diving</li>
<li>Confined Water Dives to learn basic scuba skills</li>
<li>Open Water Dives to use your skills and explore!</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/open-water-diver/">Open Water Diver</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/open-water-diver/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discover Scuba Diving</title>
		<link>/discover-scuba-diving/</link>
					<comments>/discover-scuba-diving/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 22:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1900</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Diver certification begins here. Start with PADI's online eLearning course. Move to the pool and practice your new skills. Then experience four open water (ocean/lake) dives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discover-scuba-diving/">Discover Scuba Diving</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>A quick and easy introduction into what it takes to explore the underwater world. Although this is not a scuba certification course, you&#8217;ll learn all the steps it takes to be a PADI certified diver.</strong></p>
<p>Have you always wondered what it’s like to breathe underwater? If you want to try scuba diving, but aren’t quite ready to take the plunge into a certification course, Discover Scuba Diving is for you. PADI dive shops offer this program either in a pool, off a beach or from a dive boat. You can try scuba close to home or while you’re on vacation at a dive destination. While not a scuba certification course, Discover Scuba Diving is a quick and easy introduction to what it takes to explore the underwater world. To sign up for a PADI Discover Scuba Diving experience, you must be at least 10 years old. No prior experience with scuba diving is necessary, but you need to be in reasonable physical health. Are you ready to try it out? Use the event locator to find and schedule a Discover Scuba Diving experience near you.</p>
<p>You learn the basic safety guidelines and skills needed to dive under the direct supervision of a PADI Professional. If you make an open water dive, you’ll practice a few more skills in shallow water to prepare for your adventure. Get ready to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Go over the <a title="Learn About Scuba Equipment" href="https://www.padi.com/help/gear-faq">scuba equipment</a> you use to dive and how easy it is to move around underwater with your gear.</li>
<li>Find out what it’s like to breathe underwater.</li>
<li>Learn key skills that you’ll use during every scuba dive.</li>
<li>Have fun swimming around and exploring.</li>
<li>Hear about becoming a certified diver through the <a title="PADI Open Water Diver Course" href="https://www.padi.com/courses/open-water-diver">PADI Open Water Diver course</a>.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discover-scuba-diving/">Discover Scuba Diving</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/discover-scuba-diving/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ultimate 2 Day Offshore Adventure</title>
		<link>/the-ultimate-2-day-offshore-adventure/</link>
					<comments>/the-ultimate-2-day-offshore-adventure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 20:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of a lifetime opportunity to enjoy 2 Days at a unique Offshore Islands, pristine enviroment for Spearfishing, Scuba Diving and empty waves for surfing! Catering a Gourmet experience on board in our Custom grill, a weekend full of adrenaline!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultimate-2-day-offshore-adventure/">The Ultimate 2 Day Offshore Adventure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Features:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Itinerary: Departure at 10:00 PM, plus 2 days at Offshore Lacation and returning at Sunset after dinner, arriving to the Marina in the following date for breakfast.</li>
<li>2 days, 3 nights on board.</li>
<li>Airport Round Trip Transfers</li>
<li>Surfboards</li>
<li>Professional freediving/snorkel guide</li>
<li>Sportfishing &amp; spearfishing gear provided</li>
<li>Scuba Diving available upon request for certified divers</li>
<li>Full Snorkel gear</li>
<li>Underwater photos and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>All drinks and meals are included.</li>
<li>Camping setup available upon request for the night at the island</li>
<li>Live Bait and Fish Cleaning / Vacuum seal packaging available at additional cost</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultimate-2-day-offshore-adventure/">The Ultimate 2 Day Offshore Adventure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-ultimate-2-day-offshore-adventure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 DAY Blue Water Hunting Package</title>
		<link>/3-day-blue-water-hunting-package/</link>
					<comments>/3-day-blue-water-hunting-package/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 20:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Based on our many years of experience and seeing the success of our clients in blue water we consider 3 days as the ideal time investment in order to achieve your dreams of that One Fish!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/3-day-blue-water-hunting-package/">3 DAY Blue Water Hunting Package</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Includes:</h2>
<ul>
<li>3 days of hunting offshore (10 hour trip per day)</li>
<li>Full RIFFE Gear</li>
<li>Professional Guide and Captain.</li>
<li>Live Bait</li>
<li>Fish cleaning</li>
<li>Food &amp; Drinks Included.</li>
<li>Airport round trip transfers</li>
<li>Vacuum seal packaging available at additional cost*</li>
<li>Underwater photos</li>
<li>Extra days available if requested.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/3-day-blue-water-hunting-package/">3 DAY Blue Water Hunting Package</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/3-day-blue-water-hunting-package/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curso de Apnea!</title>
		<link>/curso-de-apnea/</link>
					<comments>/curso-de-apnea/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 20:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1870</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Deje de soñar con el mundo submarino y aprenda Apnea con nosotros! Nos comprometemos a brindarle la mejor experiencia de aprendizaje junto con PADI.</p>
<p>Precio: $5,000 pesos, mínimo 4 personas y máximo 6.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/curso-de-apnea/">Curso de Apnea!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>El curso PADI Freediver consta de tres fases principales:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>El desarrollo de conocimientos sobre los fundamentos del freediving</li>
<li>Sesión en aguas confinadas para aprender técnicas de Apnea así como apnea estática y dinámica. Objetivo – apnea estática de 90 segundos y apnea dinámica de 25 metros/80 pies.</li>
<li>Sesiones en aguas abiertas para practicar inmersión libre y freedives con peso constante. Objetivo &#8211; freedive con peso constante a 10 metros/30 pies.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Incluye:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Curso de 2 días</li>
<li>Fotos y videos bajo el agua</li>
<li>Materiales en línea y tarjeta de certificación</li>
<li>Instructor profesional PADI certificado de apnea</li>
<li>Bebidas y Snacks</li>
<li>Día adicional para apnea con tarifa especial si se solicita.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/curso-de-apnea/">Curso de Apnea!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/curso-de-apnea/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coastal Foraging</title>
		<link>/coastal-foraging/</link>
					<comments>/coastal-foraging/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1841</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Join our marine biologist/guide and Four Seasons chef for a coastal walk in search of edible sea life amongst a world of sea stars and seaweed... native swimmers and scuttlers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coastal-foraging/">Coastal Foraging</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Reading the seasons, timing the tides, and knowing your sea life can reveal a smorgasbord of healthy food for foraging. With the help of your guide and chef, you too can learn to recognize valuable sea life, learn their uses, and get to know some key recipes.</p>
<p>Gathering and consuming wild plants and animal instills a greater respect for the environment that is their home. This experience reconnects us to the origins of our food and vividly illustrates our dependance on nature for our survival. You will not need to get into the ocean to take part in this empowering experience; however water shoes will be provided.<br />
Step away from online recipes and store bought ingredients and into the forgotten reality that the earth provides everything we need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coastal-foraging/">Coastal Foraging</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/coastal-foraging/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scuba Diving Excursions</title>
		<link>/scuba-diving-excursions/</link>
					<comments>/scuba-diving-excursions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 16:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our certified and experienced PADI dive staff will lead you through the dive experience of a lifetime and assure that not a single encounter goes missed. Travel out of the protected bay and into the open ocean in style and comfort aboard our custom dive fleet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scuba-diving-excursions/">Scuba Diving Excursions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>The stuff scuba dreams are made up&#8230;</h3>
<p><img class="alignleft wp-image-1827 size-thumbnail" src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/230-2307314_padi-logo-transparent-background-hd-png-download-150x150.png" alt="" width="150" height="150" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/230-2307314_padi-logo-transparent-background-hd-png-download-150x150.png 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/02/230-2307314_padi-logo-transparent-background-hd-png-download-600x600.png 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/02/230-2307314_padi-logo-transparent-background-hd-png-download-100x100.png 100w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></p>
<p>These offshore dive sites offer both virgin reefs and pelagic big life encounters worthy of Nat Geo documentary footage; Schooling Tuna flying past, reefs swarming with sea turtles, Humpback whale mothers introducing their calves to the world, reef sharks resting within the volcanic nooks, giant manta rays visiting the reefs’ cleaning stations to be service by the most intricately colored tropical fish, even the tiniest most delicate sea horse as they hold the reef into which they seem to the untrained eye to disappear.</p>
<p>Our certified and experienced PADI dive staff will lead you through the dive experience of a lifetime and assure that not a single encounter goes missed. Travel out of the protected bay and into the open ocean in style and comfort aboard our custom dive fleet.</p>
<h3 style="clear: both;">Our Dive Sites:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>El Morro</strong><br />
Vertical pinnacles rising from the depths of over 100 feet providing a setting for almost unimaginable Marine life encounters.</li>
<li><strong>La Corbeteña</strong><br />
Two spectacular seamounts where are the biodense reef touches the open ocean&#8230;.where pelagic giants intimately meet delicate reef life.</li>
<li><strong>El Banco</strong><br />
Three underwater seamounts that lie deep enough to leave an interrupted flow of pelagic life that seem to fly overhead.</li>
<li><strong>Tres Marias Islands</strong><br />
Jewell of the Mexican pacific, the Tres Marias Island chain boast unadulterated reefs, giving us a peek into underwater world that once was.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scuba-diving-excursions/">Scuba Diving Excursions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/scuba-diving-excursions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discover Spearfishing</title>
		<link>/discover-spearfishing/</link>
					<comments>/discover-spearfishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 15:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the food web and experience the thrill of the underwater hunt. Our discover spearfishing is an extraordinary excursion for families and friends alike.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discover-spearfishing/">Discover Spearfishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You slide into the water as quietly as possible and take in the new world around you. Man, woman, girl, or boy; you are now a predator. You know your environment, recognize your prey, and have the underwater skills and cunning to bring your fish to the surface on a single breath.In an increasingly more interdependent society, who doesn’t daydream of a simple and direct relationship with our food; of recognizing our place in the earth’s order, embracing our primal nature, and celebrating the autonomy of a successful hunt and delicious meal.</p>
<p>Spearfishing, or underwater hunting, is fishing’s most selective and engaging practice; the only fishing style in which one can cross the threshold of the oceans surface to become an active part of the underwater ecosystem; blending enjoyment and exercise into a true ‘ocean to table’ experience.</p>
<p>Great for families, this Discover Spearfishing excursion is a life changing family activity that introduces your children to the complete energy cycle giving them skills and appreciation to last a lifetime.</p>
<p>Our trained spear divers will take you through the basics of underwater hunting. You will learn how to safely operate your spear and equipment, distinguish the edible fish of our reef areas, and develop the cunning and the underwater skills to stalk and shoot your first underwater catch.</p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>3-hour expedition</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit® drinks, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discover-spearfishing/">Discover Spearfishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/discover-spearfishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
