<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sportfishing &#8211; Spearmex</title>
	<atom:link href="/sportfishing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Luxury Fishing &#38; Spearfishing adventures in Punta Mita, Nayarit Mexico</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 21:49:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.6</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Inshore Fishing</title>
		<link>/inshore-fishing/</link>
					<comments>/inshore-fishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=81</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Packed with adventure and sprinkled with luxury, this in-shore fishing excursion boasts an unforgettable adventure for the whole family.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inshore-fishing/">Inshore Fishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While serious enough for experienced anglers to enjoy, this half-day expedition is ideal for families or groups looking for a casual or first-time fishing adventure. Balancing exhilarating fishing action with a leisurely cruise, this trip has something for everyone to enjoy.</p>
<p>Seasonal changes offer an enormous diversity of local marine fauna to appreciate throughout the year. Cruise Punta Mita’s coastal waters pursuing everything from jumping Spanish Mackerels and tasty Mahi-Mahi to tenacious Roosterfish (catch &amp; release species) and reef dwelling Snappers.</p>
<p>Our expert fishing staff and finest equipment insure a rewarding catch and gripping adventure for all. Onboard amenities add a touch of luxury to this trip, making it a delightful excursion for the entire family. Enjoy a ceviche prepared with your first catch of the day and paired with our exclusive Patron Experience<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> signature drinks as you revel in the natural wonders of the Pacific.</p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>4 hours expedition</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit®, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
<li>Patrón Experience</li>
<li>Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inshore-fishing/">Inshore Fishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/inshore-fishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Game Fishing</title>
		<link>/big-game-fishing/</link>
					<comments>/big-game-fishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=86</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A day-long, new exciting family adventure where you can catch your next big fish in the most spectacular offshore locations of Punta Mita. An adventure worthy of world record breaking.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-game-fishing/">Big Game Fishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This excursion is a must for any serious sportfishing angler looking for their next big catch. World Renowned in the fishing world, Punta Mita has welcomed numerous tournaments and repetitively boast world record catches. Sebastian Melani and his seasoned team at Spearmex offer a premier big game fishing adventure in luxurious style.</p>
<p>Visit offshore locations teeming with marlin, sailfish, yellow fin tuna, mahi-mahi, and more. Our fully equipped boats and professional team assure the very best chances for the catch of a lifetime. All of our expeditions are preformed with respect for the environment and billfish species are managed as catch and release only.</p>
<p>The Spearmex team caters to all, from the novice to the most experienced angler, making this a welcome expedition for family and friends. Enjoy top-notch amenities including gourmet ceviche or sashimi prepared from the day’s first catch by your personal chef and accompanied by our Patron Experience<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> signature drinks.</p>
<p><strong>Spearmex brings luxury into wild Pacific waters to create an unsurpassed deep-sea fishing adventure!</strong></p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>8-hour expedition</li>
<li>Welcome kit (soft cooler, reusable water bottle, waterproof phone case)</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Melton tackle, fish cleaning , vacuum sealing and deep freeze catch</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit, sodas) and snacks (chicken wraps, fruits selection and cookies)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</li>
<li>Patron Experience</li>
<li>Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-game-fishing/">Big Game Fishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/big-game-fishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kayak Fishing</title>
		<link>/kayak-fishing/</link>
					<comments>/kayak-fishing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 08:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=87</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This one-of-a-kind fishing experience combines the adrenaline of hooking a good catch and the challenge of maneuvering your kayak at the same time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kayak-fishing/">Kayak Fishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paddle out at dawn on out a custom-made fishing kayak for a unique, true life ‘Old Man and the Sea’ epic.</p>
<p>Our Jackson® fishing kayaks are equipped with the very best fishing equipment and experienced guides accompany you on your journey to lead you through an hour of the most unique fishing experience offered. Chance upon catches of jacks, snapper, pompano, and other coastal and reef fish while simultaneously handling your fishing vessel.</p>
<p>This excursion has gained fans all over the world due to the level of difficulty that it brings. Are you up for the challenge?</p>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>2-hour expedition</li>
<li>1 hour expedition U$D 100.00</li>
<li>HD photography and videos by GO PRO</li>
<li>Drinks (bottled water, electrolit®, sodas)</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Guide and Deckhands</li>
<li>Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kayak-fishing/">Kayak Fishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spearmex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/kayak-fishing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
