<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Expedition | Spearmex</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/expedition/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Luxury Fishing &#38; Spearfishing adventures in Punta Mita, Nayarit Mexico</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:30:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/favicon-100x100.png</url>
	<title>Expedition | Spearmex</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Offshore Scuba Diving</title>
		<link>/product/offshore-scuba-diving/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=3464</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Explore pristine reefs and encounter breathtaking marine life, from schooling tuna and sea turtles to humpback whales with their calves, reef sharks, and giant manta rays. Even the tiniest seahorses hide among the vibrant reefs.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The stuff scuba dreams are made up…</strong></p>
<p>These offshore dive sites offer both virgin reefs and pelagic big life encounters worthy of Nat Geo documentary footage; Schooling Tuna flying past, reefs swarming with sea turtles, Humpback whale mothers introducing their calves to the world, reef sharks resting within the volcanic nooks, giant manta rays visiting the reefs’ cleaning stations to be service by the most intricately colored tropical fish, even the tiniest most delicate sea horse as they hold the reef into which they seem to the untrained eye to disappear.</p>
<p>Our certified and experienced PADI dive staff will lead you through the dive experience of a lifetime and assure that not a single encounter goes missed. Travel out of the protected bay and into the open ocean in style and comfort aboard our custom dive fleet.</p>
<p><strong>Top Dive Sites:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">El Morro: Towering pinnacles rising from depths of over 100 feet, home to incredible marine life.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">La Corbeteña: Two seamounts where the reef meets the open ocean, attracting pelagic giants.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">El Banco: Three deep seamounts offering uninterrupted pelagic encounters.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tres Marías Islands: A pristine island chain with untouched reefs, a glimpse into the underwater world as it once was.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Book your offshore diving adventure today!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Departure time from Marina la Cruz and Punta Mita: 09:00 am.</span></p>
<p><strong>Boats available:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 2, 30 ft power catamaran, center console</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 5, 35 ft, with cabin, bathroom and tuna tower</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sport fishing yacht 45 ft, with cabin, bathroom, and flybridge.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Features</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2 Tanks</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">6 hours experience</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Drinks; bottled water, electrolytes and sodas.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Snacks, fruit and banana bread.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunset Cruise</title>
		<link>/product/sunset-cruise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 19:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=2315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bask in the luxury of our yachts while you enjoy nature’s finest reminder of the here and now... the gentle slipping of the sun into the ocean.
<ul>
 	<li>35 feet power catamaran</li>
 	<li>2 Hours</li>
 	<li>Price per boat (max 6 people)</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the magic of a perfect sunset as you sail across the crystal-clear waters of the bay. Our Sunset Cruise invites you to enjoy an exclusive journey where luxury and serenity blend with the golden, pink, and orange hues painting the sky as the sun sets.</p>
<p>Share unforgettable moments with your partner, family, or friends while toasting with a selection of premium drinks, from refreshing cocktails to sparkling wine. Relax in the comfort of our spacious catamaran, designed to offer a unique experience with panoramic coastal views.</p>
<p>As we glide through the ocean, you’ll be captivated by the breathtaking scenery: the silhouette of the mountains, golden beaches, and the sun’s reflection merging with the sea. And if you visit between December and March, you’ll have the chance to witness a spectacular natural show—the humpback whales breaching and singing as they grace us with their majestic presence.</p>
<p>Discover the perfect balance of adventure and relaxation aboard our Sunset Cruise. Let the ocean breeze carry you away, enjoy the soothing sound of the waves, and create unforgettable memories as the sun bids farewell on the horizon.</p>
<p><strong>Food:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Pastries (Banana Bread)</li>
<li>Tropical Fruit Platter</li>
<li>Snacks (Veggie Chips, Pretzels, Organic Chips, Peanuts)</li>
<li>Cold Cuts and Cheese Platter</li>
<li>Crudites with hummus</li>
<li>Guacamole and chips</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Drinks:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Water</li>
<li>San Pellegrino Sparkling Mineral Water (Flavors: Natural, Lemonade, Orange, Clementine)</li>
<li>Electrolites</li>
<li>Domestic Beers</li>
<li>Premium Tequila, White Wine (Sauvignon Blanc)</li>
<li>Regular and Diet Coke and Topo chico</li>
<li>For Kids Apple and Berries Juices.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Features</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Full Snorkel gear</li>
<li>Sportfishing gear provided upon request</li>
<li>Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</li>
<li>Specially trained, bilingual and experienced deckhands and Captain</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Fleet Available:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Spearo 5 &#8211; 35 feet power boat with cabin &#8211; Up to 6 people</li>
<li>Riviera 45 &#8211; 45 feet yatch with fly bridge &#8211; Up to 8 people</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Departure Time</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Sunset Cruise departing from Marina La Cruz
<ul>
<li>Winter: 5:00  pm to 7:00pm</li>
<li>Summer: 6:00pm to 8:00pm</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Local Snorkel Cruise</title>
		<link>/product/local-snorkel-cruise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 18:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=2273</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Explore this beautiful Mexican paradise in style!
<ul>
 	<li>24 Feet power boat (Spearo 12)</li>
 	<li>3 hours</li>
 	<li>Price per boat (max 4 people)</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embark on an unforgettable adventure in the crystal-clear waters off the coast of Punta de Mita with our Whale Watching and Snorkel Tour. This immersive experience offers the rare opportunity to witness the majestic humpback whales as they migrate through the waters of Banderas Bay, one of the best locations in the world for whale watching. From December to March, you&#8217;ll have the chance to see these incredible creatures up close, as they breach, tail slap, and spy-hop right next to your boat.</p>
<ul>
<li>Up-close whale watching in Banderas Bay (seasonal from December to March)</li>
<li>Snorkeling in crystal-clear waters, home to vibrant marine life</li>
<li>Professional guides with expert knowledge of local wildlife</li>
<li>Personalized experience</li>
<li>Perfect for all ages and skill levels</li>
<li>3 and 4 hour adventure</li>
</ul>
<h3>Departure Time:</h3>
<ul>
<li>9:00 AM and 2:00 PM.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Meeting point:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Sea Breeze</strong><br />
St Regis Beach Club. Access only for Punta Mita Owners, Residents or if you are staying inside the gated community</li>
<li><strong>Spearmex Shop  (Punta de Mita)</strong><br />
Av. Anclote #200 Local 4 y 5, Col. Corral del Risco, Punta de Mita, next to Hectors Kitchen and half block from Tuna Blanca</li>
<li><strong>Marina La Cruz de Huanacaxtle</strong><br />
Dock 1 &#8211; Marlin 39-A, 63734 Cruz de Huanacaxtle, Nay.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Fleet Available:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Custom 24ft with Full Shade Panga– Up to 4 people</li>
<li>Pro Sport Cat 30ft Powerboat – Up to 6 people</li>
<li>Everglades 35 &#8211; Up to 8 people</li>
<li>Riviera 45 &#8211; Up to 12 people</li>
<li>Triton Catamaran: Up to 45 people.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Amenities:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Food:</strong>
<ul>
<li>Pastries (Banana Bread)</li>
<li>Tropical Fruit Platter</li>
<li>Snacks</li>
<li>Cold Cuts and Cheese Platter</li>
<li>Fresh Ceviche and Sashimi</li>
<li>Guacamole and chips</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Drinks:</strong>
<ul>
<li>Water</li>
<li>San Pellegrino Sparkling Mineral Water (Flavors: Natural, Lemonade, Orange, Clementine)</li>
<li>Electrolites</li>
<li>Domestic Beers</li>
<li>Premium Tequila, White Wine (Sauvignon Blanc)</li>
<li>Regular and Diet Coke and Topo chico</li>
<li>For Kids Apple and Berries Juices.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>What to Bring:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Sunblock</li>
<li>Hat</li>
<li>Bathing Suit</li>
</ul>
<p>Join us for a once-in-a-lifetime adventure in Punta de Mita, where the beauty of the ocean and its creatures will leave you in awe.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whale Watching &#038; Hidden Beach</title>
		<link>/product/whale-watching/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 18:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=2244</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Experience whale watching in Banderas Bay and visit the Marietas Islands' Hidden Beach. Enjoy snorkeling, pristine nature, and an exclusive, guided 4-hour adventure.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Whale Watching &amp; Marietas Islands with Hidden Beach Tour</h2>
<p>Embark on a thrilling adventure to explore two of the most iconic wonders of the Pacific: the majestic humpback whales of Banderas Bay and the stunning Marietas Islands, home to the world-famous Hidden Beach. This unforgettable tour combines nature’s most awe-inspiring creatures with one of the most exclusive and surreal beaches in the world.</p>
<ul>
<li>Whale watching in Banderas Bay (seasonal from December to March) with expert guides</li>
<li>Visit to the Marietas Islands, a UNESCO Biosphere Reserve</li>
<li>Access to the Hidden Beach with a additional local panga to follow the rules of the national park — a secluded, pristine beach inside a volcanic crater</li>
<li>Snorkeling in the rich marine ecosystems around the islands</li>
<li>Intimate and personalized experience</li>
<li>Professional and knowledgeable guides to ensure your safety and enjoyment</li>
<li>4 hour experience</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Departure Time: </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>9:00 AM and 2:00 PM.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Meeting point:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Sea Breeze</strong>
<ul>
<li><em>St Regis Beach Club. Access only for Punta Mita Owners, Residents or if you are staying inside the gated community</em></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Spearmex Shop (Punta de Mita)</strong>
<ul>
<li><em>Av. Anclote #200 Local 4 y 5, Col. Corral del Risco, Punta de Mita, next to Hectors Kitchen and half block from Tuna Blanca</em></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Marina La Cruz de Huanacaxtle</strong>
<ul>
<li><em>Dock 1 &#8211; Marlin 39-A, 63734 Cruz de Huanacaxtle, Nay.</em></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Fleet Available:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Pro Sport Cat 30ft Powerboat</strong> – Up to 6 people</li>
<li><strong>Everglades 35</strong> &#8211; Up to 8 people</li>
<li><strong>Riviera 45</strong> &#8211; Up to 12 people</li>
<li><strong>Triton Catamaran:</strong> Up to 45 people.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Food:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Pastries (Banana Bread)</li>
<li>Tropical Fruit Platter</li>
<li>Snacks</li>
<li>Cold Cuts and Cheese Platter</li>
<li>Fresh Ceviche and Sashimi</li>
<li>Guacamole and chips</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Drinks:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Water</li>
<li>San Pellegrino Sparkling Mineral Water (Flavors: Natural, Lemonade, Orange, Clementine)</li>
<li>Electrolites</li>
<li>Domestic Beers</li>
<li>Premium Tequila, White Wine (Sauvignon Blanc)</li>
<li>Regular and Diet Coke and Topo chico</li>
<li>For Kids Apple and Berries Juices.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>What to Bring:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Sunblock</li>
<li>Hat</li>
<li>Bathing Suit</li>
</ul>
<p>Prepare to be amazed by the wonders of the ocean and the unparalleled beauty of the Marietas Islands and its hidden treasures!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jet Ski &#038; Tow Sports</title>
		<link>/product/jet-ski/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 17:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=2060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enjoying tow sports from our JetSki has never been easier thanks to three exclusive features including the retractable LinQ ski pylon, ski mode, and wakeboard rack.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Sea Doo Wake Pro 230</h2>
<p>Enjoying tow sports from our JetSki has never been easier thanks to three exclusive features including the retractable LinQ ski pylon, ski mode, and wakeboard rack.</p>
<p>The first fully-integrated waterproof Audio System will keep the fun going anywhere you go, standard with 100 watts of total system power, fully-waterproof performance, Bluetooth connectivity, and external playback controls to ensure the perfect song is always on!</p>
<p><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>BRP Audio &#8211; Premium Soundsystem</li>
<li>Direct-access front storage</li>
<li>Watertight phone compartment</li>
<li>Boarding Ladder</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>ACTIVITIES AVAILABLE</strong></h3>
<p><strong>FOIL SURFING</strong></p>
<p>Foilsurfing shifts that paradigm and completely redefines what kind of wave will get your heart racing.</p>
<p>Your first foilsurfing lesson takes place in the waterway where the water is flat, so you can learn the basics of riding a foilboard. Once you&#8217;ve got the hang of foiling in flat water, we will advance you to the next step by taking you out into the ocean where we&#8217;ll begin towing into ocean swell.</p>
<p>This is where you will learn how to catch and ride the swell energy and begin to learn the mechanics of pumping the foil to stay on the swell.</p>
<p><strong>WIND FOILING</strong></p>
<p>Windfoiling is relatively easy to learn, especially if you already know how to windsurf. The first few runs will be challenging as you need to get used to controlling the foil with small body movements. Pretty quickly you will finally understand the influence of your body weight and find the right position on your board.</p>
<p>Windfoiling is also far less physically demanding than windsurfing. Since you&#8217;ll be flying above the sea, there is no friction between the water and your board. The hydrodynamic drag is minimal and you don&#8217;t get battered around by the waves.</p>
<p>This makes windfoiling suitable for everybody, regardless of age or gender.</p>
<p><strong>WAKE FOILING</strong></p>
<p>Learning to how to foil is easy when you book a lesson with one of our experienced and knowledgeable coaches. Trying to figure it out on your own, on the other hand, can be a deeply intimidating and frustrating experience. When you learn with us, we&#8217;ll get you up on the foil the faster and safer way. Getting your first rides behind a jet ski dramatically simplifies and accelerates the learning curve.</p>
<p>Instead of guessing and learning by trial and error, our coaches will teach you the mechanics of foiling through a gradual progression on equipment that makes it as easy and safe as possible. Whether you are interested in foiling with a kite, a boat, or in the waves, we can get you where you want to go.</p>
<p><strong>WAKEBOARDING</strong></p>
<p>The wake board is another popular choice on the water and you don’t have to be able snowboard or water ski to enjoy wakeboarding. It’s a sport that provides a sense of achievement and thrills even for even complete novices. Do not miss the opportunity of a Wakeboarding sesion.</p>
<p>Allow yourself to relax allows your body to make changes and shift weight far easier than if you are tensed up. Before you are towed, you will start with the cable in hand and your knees drawn up as far as possible to your chest. Your arms should be stretched out in front of you.</p>
<p>Wakeboarding is all about going with the flow; once you feel the cable being pulled, allow yourself to roll forward slightly and keep your knees locked as your speed increases. Before you know it, you will be standing upright!</p>
<p><strong>DONUT RIDING</strong></p>
<p>An inflatable tube which is designed to be like a donut is towed behind a watercraft. Immerse yourself in the experience of speed and thrill as you glide on the water. You not only get to be on the Donut while having a time of your life but you’ll also be able to soak in the amazing coastline.</p>
<p>This amazing activity shouldn’t be missed especially by those who live for the high speed and thrill. With its twist and turns, high speed, it’ll surely test your strength while having the wildest ride of your life.</p>
<p>Our donut ride is a great choice for anyone new to watersports. It is also an amazing way to introduce young kids to the world of watersports. As this activity is suitable for everyone, we take extra measures for children and new adventurers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Local Guided Scuba Diving</title>
		<link>/product/local-guided-scuba-diving/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 16:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=1824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our certified and experienced PADI dive staff will lead you through the dive experience of a lifetime and assure that not a single encounter goes missed. Travel out of the protected bay and into the open ocean in style and comfort aboard our custom dive fleet.
<ul>
 	<li>24 Feet power boat</li>
 	<li>3 hours</li>
 	<li>Price per Person (min 2 people)</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Explore Punta Mita’s Local Dive Sites</strong></p>
<p>Located just 10 to 20 minutes by boat from Punta Mita, these local dive sites are perfect for divers seeking a convenient yet rewarding underwater adventure. Dive depths range from 30 to 70 feet (9 to 21 meters), accommodating all skill levels, from beginner to experienced divers. The water temperature averages between 77°F and 84°F (25°C to 29°C), ensuring a pleasant experience year-round.</p>
<p>These nearshore sites include El Malinal, El Guano, La Ahogada, among others, offering diverse underwater landscapes. Divers can encounter schools of colorful fish such as king angelfish, damselfish, and parrotfish, as well as moray eels, pufferfish, and stingrays hiding among the rocks and coral. Lucky divers may also spot octopuses, seahorses, and even sea turtles passing through these vibrant reefs.</p>
<p>With short travel times, incredible marine biodiversity, and stunning underwater scenery, Punta Mita’s local dive sites offer an ideal combination of accessibility and natural beauty.</p>
<p>We offer shared departures Wednesday and Saturday at 8:30 AM from El Anclote and 9:00 AM from Beach Club Sea Breeze minimun 2 people, making it easy to start your underwater adventure at a time and place that’s convenient for you. $270.00 usd per person.</p>
<p>Private Experiences up to 4 people, from Marina la Cruz and Punta Mita: 09:00 am or 02:00 pm. $1,082.00 usd.</p>
<p><strong>Boats available:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">24 ft custom boat with shade. Up o 4 people.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Features</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2 Tanks</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">4 hours experience</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Drinks; bottled water, electrolytes and sodas.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Snacks, fruit and banana bread.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Deckhands</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discover Spearfishing</title>
		<link>/product/discover-spearfishing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 15:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dive into the food web and experience the thrill of the underwater hunt. Our discover spearfishing is an extraordinary excursion for families and friends alike.
<ul>
 	<li>24 Feet power boat (Spearo 12)</li>
 	<li>3 hours</li>
 	<li>Price per person (min 2 people)</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Experience fishing like never before, become one with the ocean and take snorkeling to a whole new level. A very simple program that consists of 3 steps.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Step 1: Briefing on the beach (go through all the technical names of each part of the equipment, how to use the equipment properly and safety protocols)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step 2: Shallow water practice (Practice step 1)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step 3: Reef Hunting (Head off to the nearest reefs to catch lunch)</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Type of fish: Snappers, Triggerfish, Jacks, Pompanos</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Departure times from Marina la Cruz and Punta Mita: 09:00 am and 02:00 pm</span></p>
<p><strong>Boats available:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 12, 24 ft custom boat with shade.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Features:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">3-hour expedition.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Minimum age: 10 years, Minimum of 2 participants.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Drinks; bottled water, electrolytes and sodas.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearfishing equipment by Riffe International</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specially trained, bilingual, and experienced Captain and Spearos</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blue Water Hunting</title>
		<link>/product/blue-water-hunting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=484</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This excursion is the perfect combination of on-board luxury and raw adrenaline as we head into the world class fishing waters of Pacific Mexico for the ultimate open ocean spearfishing adventure.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="row">
<div class="col-md-9">
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our most outstanding experience, the Blue Water Hunting expedition is unlike any other.   Offshore is where fish stories need no exaggeration. Dozens of Mahi-mahi circling under a driftwood log, Marlin moving in and out of a bait ball, Yellowfin Tuna schools barreling past as you dive into the open blue,  and of course the pure adrenaline rush of a thrilling and successful hunt.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Type of fish: Yellowfin tuna, Wahoo, Blue, Black and Striped Marlin and Cubera Snappers</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Departure times from Marina la Cruz and Punta Mita: 07:00 am or 08:00 am.</span></p>
<p><strong>Boats available:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 2, 30 ft power catamaran, center console.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 5, 35 ft, with cabin, bathroom and tuna tower</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sport fishing yacht 45 ft, with cabin, bathroom, and flybridge.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Features</strong>:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">8-hour expedition.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Drinks; bottled water, electrolytes, sodas, beers and Tequila.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Snacks, fruit and banana bread.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Full lunch menú to choose.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board with your first catch.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearfishing equipment by Riffe international</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Spearos</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="col-md-3">
<p style="text-align: center;"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-1800 size-full aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna.png" alt="" width="437" height="218" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna.png 437w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/yellowfin-tuna-300x150.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 437px) 100vw, 437px" /><br />
Yellowfin Tuna/Atun Amarilla</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-1799 size-medium aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-300x124.png" alt="Mahi Mahi/Dorado" width="300" height="124" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi-300x124.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/mahi-mahi.png 465w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><br />
Mahi Mahi/Dorado</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-1797 size-full aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo.png" alt="Wahoo/Wahoo" width="465" height="140" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo.png 465w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/07/wahoo-300x90.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 465px) 100vw, 465px" /><br />
Wahoo/Wahoo</p>
</div>
</div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inshore Guided Spearfishing</title>
		<link>/product/spearfishing-inshore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tropical reefs, thrilling spear opportunities, sunrises/sunsets, and family fun; this spearfishing excursion is chock full of memorable adventure for all.
<ul>
 	<li>24 feet power boat (Spearo 12)</li>
 	<li>4 hours</li>
 	<li>Price per boat (max 4 people)</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This half-day excursion is excellent for the whole family and/or groups of friends.  For the best hunting opportunity, either head out at dawn for an early morning on the reef or enjoy the prime-time afternoon hours complete with a spectacular Pacific sunset on the ride back to port. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Up your game with valuable local knowledge from our spear guides on the reef’s edible fish, their behavior and terrain, and the appropriate gear and techniques for each species.  Refine your camouflage and ambush techniques while searching the reef’s caves for delicious snapper species, or get into the action as jacks or Spanish mackerels raid the reef edge.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Type of fish: Snappers, Almaco jacks, Triggerfish, Roosterfish, Pompanos and Mahi Mahi.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Departure times from Marina la Cruz and Punta Mita: 09:00 am and 02:00 pm.</span></p>
<p><strong>Boats available:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 2, 30 ft power catamaran, center console.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 5, 35 ft, with cabin, bathroom and tuna tower</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sport fishing yacht 45 ft, with cabin, bathroom, and flybridge.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Features:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">4 hours expedition.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Drinks; bottled water, electrolytes, sodas, beers and Tequila.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Snacks, fruit and banana bread.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board with your first catch</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearfishing equipment by Riffe international</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Spearos</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inshore Fishing</title>
		<link>/product/inshore-fishing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorge Gallegos]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=81</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Packed with adventure and sprinkled with luxury, this in-shore fishing excursion boasts an unforgettable adventure for the whole family.
<ul>
 	<li>30 feet power boat (Spearo Two)</li>
 	<li>4 hours</li>
 	<li>Price per boat (max 6 people)</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While serious enough for experienced anglers to enjoy, this half-day expedition is ideal for families or groups looking for a casual or first-time fishing adventure.  Balancing exhilarating fishing action with a leisurely cruise, this trip has something for everyone to enjoy. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Departure times from Marina La Cruz and Punta Mita: 09:00 am and 02:00 pm.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Type of fish: Snappers, Almaco jacks, Triggerfish, roosterfish, pompanos, Mahi Mahi and Sailfish.</span></p>
<p><strong>Boats available:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 2, 30 ft power catamaran, center console.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearo 5, 35 ft, with cabin, bathroom and tuna tower</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sport fishing yacht 45 ft, with cabin, bathroom, and flybridge.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Features</strong>:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">4 hours expedition</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Drinks; bottled water, electrolytes, sodas, beers and Tequila.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Snacks, fruit and banana bread.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fresh ceviche and/or sashimi on board with your first catch</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Safety gear on every boat (life jackets and marine first aid kit)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sportfishing Custom Seeker rods and Avet reels, top of the line terminal tackle.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specially trained, bilingual and experienced Captain and Anglers.</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
